Young puss playing war games, he wanted love, but he only made more pain, poor thing.
年轻的家伙玩着战争游戏，他想要爱情，但只收获了更多的痛苦，可怜的家伙。
Young puss playing war games, he wanted love, but he only made more pain.
年轻的家伙玩着战争游戏，他想要爱情，但只收获了更多的痛苦。
Picture my soul, climbing out an infinite hole, where niggas die over pride and live for the dough.
画出我的灵魂，爬出无尽的洞穴，那里的人因骄傲而死，为财而活。
If I survive, then I'll strive to hit with the flow, hoping these waves are paid, but the ripples are slow.
如果我幸存，我会努力跟上节奏，希望这些波澜会得到回报，但波纹来的很慢。
And I'm conflicted with no digits to show, but fantasy's a frivolous hose, gripping this pole, the temperature's low.
但内心矛盾，指针无踪，幻想是个挥霍的水龙头，紧抓着这根杆，温度低。
But you know that ain't stopping lil' nigga from sliding like the tides on a whip in the snow.
但你知道小家伙不会被阻挡，像潮水在雪中滑动。
Vicious for show, tip-torn around the abyss with sticks blowing.
残忍地表演，指尖在深渊中游走，棍棒抽打。
Pissed pole with attention to glitz, the wrist glowing. Face tits from rent owing, fist clenched when niggas diss.
用关注换光彩，手腕闪亮，欠租金的脸，拳头紧握，当小家伙不爽。
But since knowing, lives expire when niggas' pride gets hide in the vocal range, inside the rise vocal chain.
但自知后，生命消逝，骄傲埋藏在音域内，上升的声线内。
My road to fame is rife with spikes and broken lanes and tolls I can't afford, but I won't complain.
我成名的道路布满刺和断裂的道路，我负担不起的费用，但我不会抱怨。
I know the more I gotta struggle is the more I gain. Post-traumatic stress on an immature brain,
我知道我挣扎得越多，我收获得越多。创伤后应激反应在不成熟的脑海中，
Leaves another corpse, young pup playing war games. Now he's handcuffed, old lady saying poor thing, poor thing.
又是一具尸体，年轻的家伙玩着战争游戏。现在他被铐住了，老妇人说可怜的家伙，可怜的家伙。
Young pups playing war games. He wanted love, but he only made more pain, poor thing.
年轻的家伙玩着战争游戏。他想要爱情，但只收获了更多的痛苦，可怜的家伙。
Young pups playing war games. He wanted love, but he wanna get some shit off of my stunner.
年轻的家伙玩着战争游戏。他想要爱情，但想从我这儿摆脱一些事情。
This nigga back home been talkin' slick and I done heard him. You get your name gone, niggas like that gon' throw their dirt on.
这小子在家说话溜，我听过。你的名声被毁了，那些家伙会把他们的脏话扔给你。
You make you some coins, niggas gon' act like you ain't earned them. He talk like he live, but I remember him from high school.
你赚了钱，那些家伙会表现得好像你没有赚到。他说话像他活着，但我记得他是从高中来的。
Man deep down inside, know he a bitch, I wanna hurt him. I know that's my pride, I carry it just like a burden.
男人内心深处，知道他是个婊子，我想伤害他。我知道那就是我的骄傲，我带着它就像背着一个负担。
When egos is flared, beware that's when they close your curtain. That's when they close your curtain. That's when they close your curtain.
当自尊心被点燃时，当心他们为你拉上帷幕。当心他们为你拉上帷幕。当心他们为你拉上帷幕。
Many nights a nigga didn't eat, punk bitch. Rent old damn it was on the street, punk bitch.
许多个夜晚，这个家伙没吃过饭，屁精。房租老天，街上的房租，屁精。
One of the western unions from you and I needed, punk bitch. All of a sudden I'm buzzin', oh now it's B-Punk.
从我们之间一个西联会，屁精。突然我开始嗡嗡作响，哦现在是B-屁精。
Get fucked by your mesquite, punk bitch. I knew UA before you was at the street, punk bitch.
你的夹竹桃强奸了你，屁精。我之前就知道UA比你早出现在街上，屁精。
Started rollin' with niggas that's packin' heat, punk bitch. You more like me than them niggas.
开始和那些拿枪的家伙混在一起，屁精。你比我更像他们。
You still invited with tattoos on your physique, punk bitch. In that lingo you added that how you speak, punk bitch.
你依然邀请了有纹身的身体，屁精。在那种语言中，你增加了你的说话方式，屁精。
And you grew up with both your parents to teach, punk bitch. So how the fuck all of a sudden you turnin' G, punk bitch.
你父母双全，教你长大，屁精。所以你怎么突然变得G，屁精。
You a slave to the peer pressure, you weak, punk bitch. You ain't claimin' no real section, your street wasn't lit.
你是同伴压力的奴隶，软弱，屁精。你没有声称任何真正的位置，你的街区并不光明。
Made your shit look like mine with hella tree trunks, bitch. Moved a four-cell drive and it was peace, bitch.
用无数的树干让我的东西看起来更好，婊子。搬动四格车，一切平和，婊子。
Till domestic turned violent and the key just switched. In the back of my mind I gotta be somethin', bitch.
直到家庭暴力变得暴力，钥匙就变了。我内心深处必须成为某人，婊子。
That's when I started rhymin' and makin' beats, son, bitch. Way before you was lyin' bout touchin' keys, son, bitch.
那是我开始创作并制作曲子，儿子，婊子。在你假装触碰键盘之前很久。
Heard you say I ain't real, that's your belief, punk bitch. Well, look, I'm back in the village so we can see, punk bitch.
我听说你并不真实，那是你的信念，屁精。好吧，看看，我回到了村庄，我们可以看看，屁精。
Gonna shoot me the fair one when we meet, punk bitch. And don't be bringin' no hammers.
当我们见面时，我会给你发一封公正的信。别带锤子。
On the war games, he gon' let love for the only man fight another day. And if I take a hell, I won't feel no way.
在战争游戏中，他让爱为唯一的人而战。如果我遭受地狱，我不会有任何感觉。
Hey, what's up? Hey, what's up? Yeah, what's good? Hey, what's up? What's up? How you been?
喂，你好？喂，你好？是的，好？喂，你好？你好？你怎么样？
Your call has been forwarded to voicemail. The person you're trying to re-
你的来电已转至语音信箱。你尝试重新拨打的人-